SATYAJIT MONDAL

Full Stack Software Developer

Portfolio: <u>satyajitmondal.com</u>
Contact: +8801917801124

E-mail: satyajit.cse@yahoo.com

Skype: live:satyajit.cse

Address: Mirpur-1, Dhaka 1216



PERSONAL STATEMENT

I'm an experienced full stack software developer who has built and scaled user focused web applications and services. I'm also passionate about build things, solve problems, agile methodologies, and collaboration techniques that help multidisciplinary teams grow and build better product.

KEY SKILLS

I've worked with multiple technologies so far like

- HTML5 - Laravel

- CSS3 - Vue js

- JavaScript - Nuxt js

- MySQL - Node is

- PHP - Linux

EDUCATION

- B.Sc (Hons) Computer Science and Engineering

Daffodil International University

Batch: 40TH, (2015-2018)

CGPA: 3.09 out of 4.0

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

Certified in Web Application Development-PHP

BITM (Basis Institute of Technology & Management)

Batch: PHP-72, (15/11/2017 to 17/02/2018)

EMPLOYMENT

<u>January 2020 – Present</u>

Software Engineer | Netcoden | Dhaka

- Develop and maintain the Forexcrm.ca that a Customer relationship management (CRM) by multiple backend language
- Pull financial data dynamically from a meta data 4 (MT4) server using a backend API
- Integrate different kinds of payment gateway to collect payments and support SAAS based software forex CRM.

February 2019 - December 2019

Full Stack Software Developer | Regfire Solutions LTD | Dhaka

- Developed a web application Human Resource Management (HRM) from scratch for codecanyon marketplace.
- Develop and maintain a live web application Point of Sale (POS) of codecanyon marketplace.

January 2017 - January 2019

Full Stack Software Developer | Freelance | Dhaka

- Designed and developed custom websites and web applications
- Collaborated and worked iteratively with clients to determine necessary project requirements

PROJECTS

One of the live project link: https://discuss.satyajitmondal.com/

Another live project link: http://pos.satyajitmondal.com/

Another live project link: http://parkdhaka.satyajitmondal.com/

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Badminton | Reading | Cooking | Traveling

REFERENCES

References are available on request.